

# **FAOCCI LAYUG**

GRAPHIC DESIGNER, WEB DESIGNER, COMPUTER TECHNICIAN



faocciworx@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/faocci

fgol.vercel.app

Yona, Guam

Hello, I'm Faocci Ghaize O. Layug, a tech and design enthusiast ready to bring my expertise to your projects. With a knack for creative problem-solving in web and graphic design, and a solid foundation in computer technology, I'm excited to contribute to a team that values innovation and excellence. Let's make a positive impact in the digital sphere together!

# **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

Graphic Designer : Self Employed

Mabalacat City Pampanga, Philippines

2016 - Present

Computer Technician : Self Employed

Mabalacat City Pampanga, Philippines

2014 - Present

Web Developer : Geopro Global Solutions Inc

Clark, Mabalacat City Pampanga, Philippines

2024

Project Manager (Capstone) : Mabalacat City College

Dolores, Mabalacat City Pampanga, Philippines

2023 - 2024

Web Designer (SHS Capstone) : Children of Fatima School Inc.

San Francisco, Mabalacat City, Philippines

2019 - 2020

## **EDUCATION**

College : Bachelor of Science Information Technology

Mabalacat City College

2020 - 2024

Senior High : Information Communication Technology

Children of Fatima Inc.

2018 - 2020

Junior High : Tinajero National High School Main

Madapdap, Mabalacat City Pampanga

2014 - 2018

## SKILLS

Web Design : Proficient in HTML, CSS, and introductory JavaScript

for creating and styling web pages. Familiar with

principles of responsive design.

Graphic Design : Skilled in using graphic design tools such as Adobe

Photoshop for image editing and Adobe Illustrator for

vector graphics.

Computer Literate : Proficient in operating systems (Windows, MacOS),

Microsoft Office Suite, internet navigation, basic troubleshooting, hardware installation, software troubleshooting, and network configuration.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Introduction to Front End Development -2/2/2024

- Machine Learning 2/1/2024
- Introduction to Artificial Intelligence 2/1/2024
- Introduction to the Fundamentals of Databases
  2/1/2024
- Introduction to Graphic Design; Basics of UI/UX - 1/31/2024
- Introduction to SQL 1/31/2024
- ➤ Introduction to PHP 1/30/2024
- Introduction to CSS 1/30/2024

- ➤ Introduction to HTML 1/30/2024
- Introduction to SEO Fundamentals Training -11/29/2023
- SEO Tutorial for Beginners 11/29/2023
- Advanced Search Engine Optimization -11/28/2023
- Cybersecurity Essentials 1/27/2023
- Introduction to Cybersecurity 1/12/2023
- ➤ Introduction to Networks 1/11/2022
- Introduction to Packet Tracer 9/13/202

#### REFFERENCE

Available upon request.

I hereby certify that all above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and ability

FAOCCI GHAIZE O. LAYUG

APPLICANT SIGNATURE